I think we could
have this very unusual
combination of very fast
GDP growth and high
unemployment or at least
underemployment or
low wage jobs a
lot of low wage
jobs high inequality I
don't think that's a
macro correct me if
I'm wrong don't think
that's a macroeconomic combination
we've ever seen before
You think of fast
growth you're like well
okay maybe there's inflation
But you're not gonna
have high unemployment when
there's fast growth I
think this technology is
a different because it's
extreme in the way
it's gonna generate value
But also because it's
moving up the cognitive
waterline there's gonna be
a whole class of
people who are think
across a of going
to have a hard
time coping And that's
really a problem we
need to